Cinderella's Sister
Episode 3
Why did you hit her?
Something like that shouldn't happen.
I did it because she is so cold toward Hyo Seon.
I see Hyo Seon annoying Eun Jo too much.
She is naturally a block of ice.
When she did it right in front of me, I was so angry I also did it without realizing.
Saying you are angry, did you raise her by beating her up every time you were angry?
You will be scolded for doing something shameful.
Don't do that again.
It drew your attention.
I was afraid you would hate my daughter for being mean to yours.
I didn't know what you would do if you noticed it.
Who noticed such a thing?
You couldn't help but see what I didn't want you to see.
You can say nothing is wrong, but you are still the landlord
and I am a widow with a child who rents monthly.
It's not just you but Hyo Seon's maternal uncle
and all the people who work in this house.
"Are you two rocks which rolled in from somewhere?" That's what those eyes say.
Say there ...
If I am seen like that, I don't know what they do to my daughter.
I feel so sorry for the pathetic thing, but I can't express that.
The feeling of beating my daughter with my hands,
you don't understand, how would you understand?
How would you understand that?
Look here, look here.
Oh dear.
Look here, Miss Kang Seok ...
Is everyone here? There's no one missing?
Any person who doesn't want to work for my new wife,
leave right now.
When ypu leave, I'll give you severance pay,
so leave immediately.
Those who cannot treat Hyo Seon's new unni as my eldest daughter,
see me now right here.
Step forward.
I've packed up a hundred times in my mind.
First. I take out the bag.
I don't need the big one.
Open the bag.
Get the underwear.
There should be two sets.
Also two pairs of socks.
One summer outfit,
one winter outfit.
A book to read if I get bored.
It's done.
I almost forgot. My entire fortune of ₩227000.
That's all. Let's go.
A place where mom isn't. Also a place where there's no bitch Hyo Seon.
I've been searching for you for a while.
Let's go.
Let's go. I'm hungry.
What the heck are you doing?
This kid makes it awkward.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Where are you going, kid?
You're not going home, are you?
You don't even know where this neighborhood is.
When I came here last summer,
I started at the beginning with a daytime ride.
I know anywhere and everywhere.
Even if I don't look like it, I am an expert so you can't hide from me.
Hey you! How can you leave when some one is injured?
I can't walk.
Are you okay? Wait up.
I think you're hurt.
Eun Jo! Wait for me!
There.
Why are you walking so quickly? I'm breathless so let's go a little slower.
Aren't you hurting? Are you hurt somewhere?
I heard a loud sound when you fell.
It looks like something is broken. Let me see.
Look at your leg! There's blood all over and you aren't aware of it?
The bleeding isn't stopping. You're in big trouble.
Really. Don't ypu feel the pain?
I hurt! How could it not hurt? But then, what of it?
I hurt but what can you do about it?
I should see if there's any internal fracture so I'll take an xray first.
Mom.
Huh?
What is it, Hyo Seon?
- Who told you that? - Huh?
The kids in my class did not tease Unni.
I asked them one by one, and they all said it.
they said they didn't make fun of our family with our different last names.
And Unni, too, .... never said that.
So, I said I am going to ask you where did you hear that said?
No, let me ask you.
I must have been mistaken.
Let's not talk about it.
Let's not bring it up again.
Yes.
Let's do that.
If you bring it up again, I'll scold you and you will be in trouble.
Doctor. is there something wrong with her sense of pain?
Even if she is foolish, it's something I can't ever understand.
If you think there is a problem in your ability to sense pain, isn't it better if you act quickly?
At that time, what language were you singing?
Huh?
The night you were singing. You were lying on your back.
Oh. That? It's a song by a Spanish singer.
But why? Did you like it? Shall I sing it?
- Is Spain far away?
- Don't you know?
It's far. It's a 12 hour plane flight to Madrid.
If I flew there to hide, no one can find me.
If you go to Spain, you must also go to Barcelona. There's Gaudi, too.
Is it hard to learn Spanish?
This girl doesn't listen until a person finishes talking.
How bizarre and interesting Gaudi's architecture is.
That's enough. Reduce the time you tutor me in math
and teach me Spanish.
What?
Please. Teach me.
Okay? This Sunday I'm going to start,
so shorten my math class by an hour and teach me Spanish
Don't get any additional fees from Hye Seon's father. Understand?
Look here.
Hey you!
I don't know Spanish. What should I do?
Have they got wheels on their tongues?
What makes the pronunciation roll like that?
Rou, rou, rollei, rool.
When can I do this?
Oh well. I'll just work on the alphabet.
Spanish is not just spoken in Spain.
Because most of South American was once colonized by Spain
currently it's the most commonly spoken language there.
It would be very useful in the future.
In that respect, studying Spanish as a second language—
-Which is the farthest?
- Huh?
Which is farther, South America or Spain?
Between them, which is farther?
Hey. You're a person who doesn't listen until the end.
Never mind. Start teaching. I'll look for a map later.
You truly are someone who doesn't listen until the end.
What kind of manners is that?
Further, why are you speaking informally when we are having a class?
All right. (Speaking formally)
Today, let's study the Spanish alphabet.
I studied the alphabet on my own last night, so let's move to the next lesson.
- What?
- I studied the alphabet last night so start with the send lesson.
Please do so. The second lesson.
The farthest place from here in South America is Ushuaia at the southern tip of Argentina.
The long narrow country in the direction of the south Pacific is Chile.
This is Argentina.
And this, precisely, is Ushuaia, at the end of the world.
As soon as I took a break from school,
I went backpacking passing through America and Mexico. When I got this far,
- I was running out of money as though a leech—
- How long did it take?
- You should let people finish—
- How long does it take to get there?
How much does it cost?
Are you going? Do you want to go to Ushuaia? Why do you want to go there?
Never mind. Let's study.
When the guests come it will be noisy.
There is no direct flight to Argentina.
You have to change flights in the US or Canada and fly to Buenos Aires.
You must travel two to three thousand kilometres from Buenos Aires to get to Ushuaia.
Studying today is hard.
Let's do it tomorrow.
By the way, is your knee okay?
Congratulations.
Yes. Yes.
This must be your first birthday with your new wife. Congratuations.
Thank you.
You're having to host a big party as soon as you arrived. You must be working so hard.
What hard work?
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Yes. This is Eun Jo's ... Hello?
To unlock the phone, enter the password.
Nui. It's Jeong Woo. Why aren't you answering?
Dad has gambled away all the money he got from you and Mom.
He said he was going to you and Mom. He just left.
I think he's going to cause a ruckus.
My heart is pounding. I think I'm going to die.
Nui, You must do well.
Am I someone you forgot?
It doesn't matter. I won't forget. Exactly what kind of parent ...
I am your card. You are my respon-
siblilty.
If you want to save it, press 1. If you want ...
Wait. Wait.
The message won't be saved.
What did she say? What did this girl say?
I will pour you a drink.
Unni.
You didn't get a gift for Dad, did you?
I ... even did it for you.
But we will use just one card.
- I don't want to.
- Unni.
Then, don't use a card. Just give the present.
I don't want to.
Unni, then ...
I want you to understand what I say.
Leave me alone.
Unni.
Why are you so scary?
Unni. This ...
Your phone keeps ringing. I think you keep getting voice messages.
Why are you touching someone else's stuff?
That's not it.
I went to our bedroom to get this and it kept vibrating on your desk.
Why are you following me?
It's boring for you to be alone.
Who is it?
Where's your uncle?
Uncle? Which one?
I mean your mother's younger brother.
Why can't you even recall something like that?
Did you give our address to that man or not?
Well... I did not give our address to that man.
But I gave him our business card.
Why? How can you do something like that?
Does your brain even work?
Didn't I say that I didn't tell him? But I only gave him our business card. That's all.
What's happened?
I just gave him our card. I don't know why the heck she was yelling at me for.
Go ahead.
- What song should I sing now?
- Just sing quickly.
Applause! Applause!
Whenever it rains, I think of that person.
The person who always remain in silence.
Who hides his love in isolation.
The person whom I cannot forget.
The person who cries alone.
- Good...
One day he asked me in the car.
Will he think of me just once?
I really want to see that person.
I still miss that person.
Hey!
Do you know that?
I taught her that song.
- So...
- Get up right now.
So...
I'll go outside.
Call me if you need anything.
I should just kill you.
Then kill me.
I really want to to kill you.
Kill me! Just kill me then!
Have you gone crazy?
Can I live without going crazy?
Without Kang Sook...
can I live without going crazy?
Go die then.
The Kang Sook you yearn for does not exist anymore.
Don't say that.
I really love your mom.
You mean the woman whom you sold?
Don't pretend to be so high and mignty.
If I were to bring you lots of money right now,
you would do the same thing.
So do you need more money?
I told you don't do that.
I missed your mother so I came here.
I'm not here for money.
Uncle, I'll carry it.
Uncle, let's go in. I said I'll bring it over.
Can you even move it by yourself?
We can carry it together then.
No matter how delicious the drink is,
I have to have my first drink.
Please go back inside. I'll carry it for you.
Will you do it?
Of course. If the host is not at his own party, it could be a mess.
Go in quickly.
Let's go.
- This guy ...
- Let's go.
Go, just go.
It's alright. They're gone.
Now that the drinking party has officially started,
you cannot stay here for long.
I'll come back right after I deliver this.
Let me just see Kang Sook once.
Do you have all of these?
What?
A house just like a palace.
With a warehouse this huge.
Aunt, Uncle, Paternal Uncle, Cousin once removed, Aunt who is father's cousin, Grandfather, Grandaunt,
Do you have such impressive backing?
If not, do something to create them.
Then the woman, you want to see so badly,
will go to you even if I try to stop her.
All you have is the chug boat that was crushed in the recent storm,
a foster child that you've picked up,
your violent tendencies, drunken behavior, and gambling debt!
Your body and mind is totally wasted.
Stop it already!
Why?
Your pride's hurt because a kid like me made fun of you?
Did you have pride to start with?!
Didn't I tell you to stop it?
Bring something that's more impressive than this!
Before that, don't you dare show yourself.
If you don't appear again,
your words saying that you love my mother, I will believe all of that.
Get lost now.
If not...
then you're just a bastard who wants money.
What's the matter?
- He's just drunk.
- Huh?
I debated just letting him continue like that and dying,
but I dragged him out from taking the steering wheel.
Now he's just out.
Can you help me kill that person?
Don't worry.
I'll send him off to catch the last train.
I should be back by dawn.
I asked you not to worry.
Go inside and eat something.
Oh, I forgot the words.
We two are going to appear and dance.
Okay.
Would it kill you to go along with me?
You're such a rude girl, really.
Hyo Seon's Father told me to go to you. Anyway, his considerate nature is an illness.
Get out.
What?
I don't even want to see you.
Get out!
Aigoo, you wretch...
Are you really crazy?
Why did you bring me here?
It'd be okay if I weren't here.
Even if I weren't here, you could have eaten and lived well on your own.
Who am I doing this for?
Do you know that I scraped my knee?
I was on my knees waiting for the miss of this household to fall asleep,
but you didn't even realize that I'd had an injury the past few days.
What? For me? Because of me?
You scraped your knee?
When?
- Fox.
- You wretch....
Don't touch me. Don't talk to me either!
Try to mess with me. Try to hit me even once!
Really, that girl.
Unni!
Unni. Where's mom?
I saw her go this way.
I gave the present to Dad.
I told him you and I prepared it together.
I...
I hate you.
You hate me too, right?
No.
I...
There's no way you can like me.
There's no way you like me, so how can you say you like me?
I really do though.
It's a lot more natural for you to hate me.
It'll be hard on you to pretend to like me when you should hate me.
So you can hate me.
Pretend you don't know me.
Don't try so hard for me too!
Unnie. No!
I'm not pretending to like you.
Really!
Believe me. I really hope you'll believe me.
You're fooling yourself.
Put your hand over your heart, and try to think about it.
Hello?
The man you saw last time will be sending Ahjusshi Jang home.
After he drops him off and that man leaves, call me.
Got it?
Nui!
What is it?
How can you just skip the greetings and get to the point?
Are you doing well? Don't you miss me?
I'm busy. I'm hanging up.
Eun Jo! Don't hang up!
What is it?
Listen to me well.
You're... my girl. I love you!
I finally confessed. What to do?
♪ In the solitude which wakes me up ♪
♪ When I wake up from an exhausted sleep ♪
Eun Jo! Ahjusshi arrived well.
♫  Because I still remember you smiling ♫
♫  I'm secretly smiling ♫
♫  Love leaves again this way ♫
♫  When the beautiful season arrives ♫
♫  In the sadness you left in the longing♫
♫  I walk this street again ♫
♫  I am living day after day ♫
♫  In your name when tears appear ♫
♫  I can't bear it, I can't laugh like this ♫
♫ I call your name again ♫
it's certainly in the Hong family register. Who is the Hong family's youngest son whose identity can't be disclosed?
The Hong family's Hong Han Seok started working at the bottom at a brewery.
The youngest son is now doing odd jobs at Gu Dae Seong's brewery.
Chairman Hong must be thinking of the succession so
he's starting his youngest son at the bottom.
That sort of scenario will be used as the description.
The father's chronic disease is getting worse.
An article will be written to appear in the Korean Economy News.
I'll write it for you, the memorandum that I'll give up the inheritance.
I'm not talking about that.
If you're telling me to get out of there, I'm not going to listen.
Who's the one that suggested I not associate myself with this family?
To me who never once wanted to be apart of this family...
you turned me into nothing in just an instance by telling me to not be associated with this family.
Just as I now don't have any power or duty to this family,
you don't have any power over the life that I live.
Who are you yelling at right now?
No matter how ill mannered you are,
How much have we done for you?
If you know how to be grateful, how could you be so disobedient with your chin up like that?
You go inside.
If you truly want to live as someone who has known relationship to this family,
go to a place that no one knows.
You should go live silently at a place that is completely unrelated to us.
You get photos taken of you in some old village drinking yourself away?
Can you swear with your hand over your heart
that this isn't against the family?
I said to go inside.
Yes. I'm going inside.
I'm going inside. If you're going to see someone, see them in the evening.
Why are you bringing someone else into the house before the meal?
Since you already let him in, clearly end your discussion.
Are you thinking of dragging out this discussion?
I got it so go inside.
Gi Hoon.
If you don't save me,
I don't have anyone else to stand by my side. Not even a single person.
From the moment I got married to the famous daughter of the Oh Seong Group,
I'm also being treated like a beggar, just like you are right now.
The Oh Seong Group forced Honju to the verge of bankruptcy
and I've brought the Hong name this far, but
my wife and your older brother
are trying to buy up all the Hongju shares.
This is not something I need to hear.
I need you.
You need me?
That's right.
You don't need me. What you need is my legal entitlement, right?
If it's combined with your shares, your portion will increase a great deal.
Gi Hoon.
Just because you said you need me...
I almost believed you for a moment.
Really...
I almost thought you really needed me.
Eat breakfast and then go.
Uncle!
How about Gi Hoon Oppa? Has he not returned yet?
He didn't contact you either?
It's because I can't get in touch with him, Uncle.
Text me when he returns. Okay?
Unni. Gi Hoon Oppa still hasn't...
Mom. Should I just turn them on their heads?
It's not like I can't do it.
For an article to appear in the Korean Financial news,
shall I give an interview?
Shall I blow them up with the story of Hong Gi Hoon,
son of Hongja Chairman Hong Han Seok and his mistress
and my terrible childhood and abuse by
by the father I can't call Father
and the brother I can't call Hyung?
Or...
should I receive something for not doing that?
What should I get from them, Mom?
Mom.
Whenever you returned from visiting their ancestors' graveyard in the past,
you would always say that place was pretty nice, didn't you?
Should I move you there?
Should I just go ahead and do that?
He's here.
He's smiling.
Eun Jo.
Come here.
He called me, "Eun Jo".
This punk.
Not listening to me again.
He called me, "Eun Jo".
He called me "Eun Jo".
Eun Jo.
I'm...
♫  I can't be without you ♫
hungry, Eun Jo.
♫ Like this for another day ♫
I'm hungry.
♫ month and year ♫
I'm starving to death.
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ My bruised heart ♫
♫Is shouting so that I can find you ♫
♫ Wherever you are ♫
♫Can't you hear my voice? Come to me. ♫
♫ Even if I live again ♫
♫ No matter how many times I'm reborn ♫
♫ I can't live a day without you ♫
He called me, "Eun Jo".
♫ The love I will protect ♫
♫ Because you're the only one I love ♫
Excuse me.
Eat.
Oppa!
Oppa. Oppa Gi Hoon.
Oppa.
What time is it?
When did you come back?
Do you know how worried I was?
I'm sorry.
- What is this?
- Huh?
Why did you set up all this food and not eat? It's all cold now.
Eat.
Oppa.
Oppa. Who am I?
Why are you acting like this when you're mine?
What kind of punk are you?
I'm sorry, Boss. Something happened suddenly.
What kind of situation was it that you couldn't even contact me?
I'm sorry. This won't happen again.
Dad! He said he was wrong.
Forgive him. Okay?
He's our tutor.
Don't scold him so scarily.
Barf.
Bye!
Unni.
You know I have a contest next week, right?
How would I know that?
I guess I didn't tell you.
Do you know I dance?
You know... mom and dad said they have somewhere to go,
so they said they might not be able to come and watch me.
Uncle is busy too.
Unni. Can you come watch me?
No.
Still... it's okay.
Dong Soo said he'll come.
Unni. Dong Soo has suddenly been friendly to me lately.
He must have had a change of heart.
I told him to come to the contest, and he asked who was coming.
So I said "I don't know".
But anyway, he said he will be going.
It worked out well, didn't it?
I know what that sigh means.
That you're getting tired of me. Right?
I know but...
No matter how much I think about it,
I don't know what you mean when you said that I'm fooling myself.
I really like you.
But you hate me, don't you?
I know. I know, but you can just continue to hate me then.
I'll continue to like you.
Even if you hate me, I won't tell you to like me.
So don't tell me to force myself to hate you.
I...
can do whatever makes you happy.
Except hate you.
You must hate to death how I keep blabbing on like this, don't you?
I know. I'm sorry.
It's Dong Soo.
Dong Soo!
♫ where you can't hold me again ♫
♫ I ask about this path again ♫
♫ Even if I want to see you ♫
Eun Jo.
♫ Even if I want to hug you ♫
♫ While looking at heaven, I pray. ♫
Eun Jo.
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I can't be without you ♫
♫ Like this, for another day, month, and year ♫
♫ It's okay, even if I'm hurt; it's okay, even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ Still, because I only love you ♫
♫ Because I only love you ♫
Oppa.
Oh, you're here?
This is for you.
Oh, thank you. You came all the way here.
You're back?
Oh my gosh! Did I pinch you? Did I pinch you?
No, no. It''s okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Surprise!
What is this?
The wallpaper in your room will be finished tomorrow.
Today is the last day we'll be sleeping in the same room together, so I threw a farewell party for you.
Sit down, Unni.
Ah. I should call Oppa Gi Hoon too.
Hold on a minute, Unni.
You...
If you like me so much, can you give me anything I ask for?
What do you want? Just tell me!
I can pick out all the stars and the moon for you too!
No matter what I take. Can you endure it all?
No matter what you take. I can endure it.
No matter what I take...
Can you like me to the very end?
I can.
Really?
I'm saying it's for real.
I don't know why I wanted to play that kind of a joke.
I was just angry somehow...
I can't pick out why in particular.
Really.
Dong Soo gave this to me, saying he wanted to date me.
Why? Didn't you say I can take anything?
As i guessed. You can't, huh?
That you'll like me.
You're fooling yourself.
Do you get it now?
Did Dong Soo really give this to you?
I told you he did.
Can I look at the card?
Card?
This is a big problem. That was in there.
No. Not the card.
Song Eun Jo! I like you. I want to date you. Let's date! I'll be good to you. - Dong Soo
I'm going crazy, really!
Lies.
What did you say?
What did you just say?
Lies!
Get lost.
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I can't be without you ♫
♫ Like this, for another day, month, and year; it's okay, even if I"m hurt ♫
♫ It's okay, even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ Still, I only love you ♫
Is this what you want?
♫Because you're the only one I love ♫
If this is what you want, I'll give it to you.
Go bring the cane! My heart hurts, you punks.
Eun Jo.
Where did you go?
I'm sorry for lying.
♫ Is shouting so that I can find you ♫
Good job. Very good job!
How can you be like this... Oppa, don't you know who it is?
♫ Wherever you are ♫
Gi Hoon, can you give me half?
Are you confident you can kill me?
Where are you going?
You said you'd go!
Who said that!